export default {
  id: 'katakana_pron',
  name: '카타카나 (발음찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: 'ア', answer: ['a'] },
    { question: 'イ', answer: ['i'] },
    { question: 'ウ', answer: ['u'] },
    { question: 'エ', answer: ['e'] },
    { question: 'オ', answer: ['o'] },
    { question: 'カ', answer: ['ka'] },
    { question: 'キ', answer: ['ki'] },
    { question: 'ク', answer: ['ku'] },
    { question: 'ケ', answer: ['ke'] },
    { question: 'コ', answer: ['ko'] },
    { question: 'サ', answer: ['sa'] },
    { question: 'シ', answer: ['shi'] },
    { question: 'ス', answer: ['su'] },
    { question: 'セ', answer: ['se'] },
    { question: 'ソ', answer: ['so'] },
    { question: 'タ', answer: ['ta'] },
    { question: 'チ', answer: ['chi'] },
    { question: 'ツ', answer: ['tsu'] },
    { question: 'テ', answer: ['te'] },
    { question: 'ト', answer: ['to'] },
    { question: 'ナ', answer: ['na'] },
    { question: 'ニ', answer: ['ni'] },
    { question: 'ヌ', answer: ['nu'] },
    { question: 'ネ', answer: ['ne'] },
    { question: 'ノ', answer: ['no'] },
    { question: 'ハ', answer: ['ha'] },
    { question: 'ヒ', answer: ['hi'] },
    { question: 'フ', answer: ['fu'] },
    { question: 'ヘ', answer: ['he'] },
    { question: 'ホ', answer: ['ho'] },
    { question: 'マ', answer: ['ma'] },
    { question: 'ミ', answer: ['mi'] },
    { question: 'ム', answer: ['mu'] },
    { question: 'メ', answer: ['me'] },
    { question: 'モ', answer: ['mo'] },
    { question: 'ヤ', answer: ['ya'] },
    { question: 'ユ', answer: ['yu'] },
    { question: 'ヨ', answer: ['yo'] },
    { question: 'ラ', answer: ['ra'] },
    { question: 'リ', answer: ['ri'] },
    { question: 'ル', answer: ['ru'] },
    { question: 'レ', answer: ['re'] },
    { question: 'ロ', answer: ['ro'] },
    { question: 'ワ', answer: ['wa'] },
    { question: 'ヲ', answer: ['wo'] },
    { question: 'ン', answer: ['n'] },
    { question: 'ガ', answer: ['ga'] },
    { question: 'ギ', answer: ['gi'] },
    { question: 'グ', answer: ['gu'] },
    { question: 'ゲ', answer: ['ge'] },
    { question: 'ゴ', answer: ['go'] },
    { question: 'ザ', answer: ['za'] },
    { question: 'ジ', answer: ['ji'] },
    { question: 'ズ', answer: ['zu'] },
    { question: 'ゼ', answer: ['ze'] },
    { question: 'ゾ', answer: ['zo'] },
    { question: 'ダ', answer: ['da'] },
    { question: 'ヂ', answer: ['ji'] },
    { question: 'ヅ', answer: ['zu'] },
    { question: 'デ', answer: ['de'] },
    { question: 'ド', answer: ['do'] },
    { question: 'バ', answer: ['ba'] },
    { question: 'ビ', answer: ['bi'] },
    { question: 'ブ', answer: ['bu'] },
    { question: 'ベ', answer: ['be'] },
    { question: 'ボ', answer: ['bo'] },
    { question: 'パ', answer: ['pa'] },
    { question: 'ピ', answer: ['pi'] },
    { question: 'プ', answer: ['pu'] },
    { question: 'ペ', answer: ['pe'] },
    { question: 'ポ', answer: ['po'] },
    { question: 'イェ', answer: ['ye'] },
    { question: 'ウァ', answer: ['wha'] },
    { question: 'ウィ', answer: ['whi'] },
    { question: 'ウェ', answer: ['whe'] },
    { question: 'ウォ', answer: ['who'] },
    { question: 'ヴァ', answer: ['va'] },
    { question: 'ヴィ', answer: ['vi'] },
    { question: 'ヴ', answer: ['vu'] },
    { question: 'ヴェ', answer: ['ve'] },
    { question: 'ヴォ', answer: ['vo'] },
    { question: 'ヴュ', answer: ['vyu'] },
    { question: 'クァ', answer: ['qa'] },
    { question: 'クィ', answer: ['qi'] },
    { question: 'クゥ', answer: ['qwu'] },
    { question: 'クェ', answer: ['qe'] },
    { question: 'クォ', answer: ['qo'] },
    { question: 'グァ', answer: ['gwa'] },
    { question: 'グィ', answer: ['gwi'] },
    { question: 'グゥ', answer: ['gwu'] },
    { question: 'グェ', answer: ['gwe'] },
    { question: 'グォ', answer: ['gwo'] },
    { question: 'チャ', answer: ['cha'] },
    { question: 'チィ', answer: ['cyi'] },
    { question: 'チュ', answer: ['chu'] },
    { question: 'チェ', answer: ['che'] },
    { question: 'チョ', answer: ['cho'] },
    { question: 'ヂャ', answer: ['dya'] },
    { question: 'ヂィ', answer: ['dyi'] },
    { question: 'ヂュ', answer: ['dyu'] },
    { question: 'ヂェ', answer: ['dye'] },
    { question: 'ヂョ', answer: ['dyo'] },
    { question: 'テャ', answer: ['tha'] },
    { question: 'ティ', answer: ['thi'] },
    { question: 'テュ', answer: ['thu'] },
    { question: 'テェ', answer: ['the'] },
    { question: 'テョ', answer: ['tho'] },
    { question: 'デャ', answer: ['dha'] },
    { question: 'ディ', answer: ['dhi'] },
    { question: 'デュ', answer: ['dhu'] },
    { question: 'デェ', answer: ['dhe'] },
    { question: 'デョ', answer: ['dho'] },
    { question: 'ツァ', answer: ['tsa'] },
    { question: 'ツィ', answer: ['tsi'] },
    { question: 'ツェ', answer: ['tse'] },
    { question: 'ツォ', answer: ['tso'] },
    { question: 'トゥ', answer: ['twu'] },
    { question: 'ドゥ', answer: ['dwu'] },
    { question: 'ファ', answer: ['fa'] },
    { question: 'フィ', answer: ['fi'] },
    { question: 'フェ', answer: ['fe'] },
    { question: 'フォ', answer: ['fo'] },
    { question: 'フャ', answer: ['fya'] },
    { question: 'フュ', answer: ['fyu'] },
    { question: 'フョ', answer: ['fyo'] }
  ]
}
